[{"answer": "Hey.", "docId": "120816pmt", "aSentId": 34, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 33}, {"answer": "Like where we are.", "docId": "120816pmt", "aSentId": 40, "question": "Is that your analysis?", "qSentId": 39}, {"answer": "Well, I don't think that I need to be prepared for it.", "docId": "120816pmt", "aSentId": 51, "question": "And what can you do about that?", "qSentId": 50}, {"answer": "Well --", "docId": "120816pmt", "aSentId": 73, "question": "Do you regret that you've got into bed with the super PACs, even though you won't admit you have?", "qSentId": 72}, {"answer": "I'll say he's setting an entirely new precedent.", "docId": "120816pmt", "aSentId": 115, "question": "Do you believe Mitt Romney when he says that he's paid at least 13 percent for the last 10 years?", "qSentId": 114}, {"answer": "Listen, I know what the vice president was saying.", "docId": "120816pmt", "aSentId": 145, "question": "Do you regret that Joe Biden used that particular phrase?", "qSentId": 144}, {"answer": "Well, I look forward -- I look forward to seeing you along the way, Piers.", "docId": "120816pmt", "aSentId": 163, "question": "It's getting exciting, isn't it, this election?", "qSentId": 162}, {"answer": "Well, Obama is a global guy.", "docId": "120816pmt", "aSentId": 181, "question": "Why would you think that President Obama would want his citizens in his own country to be second class?", "qSentId": 180}, {"answer": "Not only do I believe it but Obama says it.", "docId": "120816pmt", "aSentId": 192, "question": "You don't obviously believe that, do you?", "qSentId": 191}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, the radical Muslims have come to power in Tunisia and Egypt.", "docId": "120816pmt", "aSentId": 201, "question": "What on earth do you base that on?", "qSentId": 200}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, we're talking about Obama's motives.", "docId": "120816pmt", "aSentId": 207, "question": "I mean, that is an absolute load of filly, isn't it?", "qSentId": 206}, {"answer": "Well, of course -- well, no, no, for starters, look, Obama supported the protesters in Egypt very happily when they were demanding democracy in Egypt.", "docId": "120816pmt", "aSentId": 217, "question": "Would you be sending in American troops in Tehran?", "qSentId": 216}, {"answer": "No, I think we have to make an important distinction here.", "docId": "120816pmt", "aSentId": 226, "question": "That's not really the actions of a guy who's not worried, is it?", "qSentId": 225}, {"answer": "Well, let's start with something simple.", "docId": "120816pmt", "aSentId": 245, "question": "ORGAN: Where do you get the fact that he detests my country?", "qSentId": 244}, {"answer": "I -- it's rather troubling to me to agree with you on everything.", "docId": "120816pmt", "aSentId": 274, "question": "Any initial thoughts?", "qSentId": 273}, {"answer": "Because if American citizens and if our children and grandchildren are saddled with more debt, at some point they're going to have to pay that money back.", "docId": "120816pmt", "aSentId": 289, "question": "Why on earth would any American president actively want to put his citizens into more debt?", "qSentId": 288}, {"answer": "Well, you're attacking -- you're attacking a complete straw man.", "docId": "120816pmt", "aSentId": 308, "question": "Dinesh?", "qSentId": 307}, {"answer": "He only killed 250 Libyans before Obama initiated the use of force, yes.", "docId": "120816pmt", "aSentId": 354, "question": "You think Colonel Gadhafi has only killed -- before he was killed himself, he only killed 250 Libyans?", "qSentId": 353}, {"answer": "I'm just about to come to Syria.", "docId": "120816pmt", "aSentId": 373, "question": "How do you explain the double standard?", "qSentId": 372}, {"answer": "ILLETTE: -- No, no --", "docId": "120816pmt", "aSentId": 393, "question": "What's crazy about them?", "qSentId": 392}, {"answer": "Yes, absolutely.", "docId": "120816pmt", "aSentId": 412, "question": "You were one of his, right?", "qSentId": 411}, {"answer": "That can happen.", "docId": "120816pmt", "aSentId": 441, "question": "This is a bad move, isn't it?", "qSentId": 440}, {"answer": "It's a measurement like body weight or BMX or BMI.", "docId": "120816pmt", "aSentId": 453, "question": "Should he have that tiny amount of body fat?", "qSentId": 452}, {"answer": "You know, we call it muscle confusion.", "docId": "120816pmt", "aSentId": 464, "question": "What is different about it?", "qSentId": 463}, {"answer": "There's no one size fits all here.", "docId": "120816pmt", "aSentId": 481, "question": "Just scoff hot dogs all day?", "qSentId": 480}, {"answer": "He was in great shape when he started.", "docId": "120816pmt", "aSentId": 489, "question": "When he came to you for the first time, what shape was he in then?", "qSentId": 488}, {"answer": "Well, when I'm there, it's a very bipartisan affair.", "docId": "120816pmt", "aSentId": 497, "question": "Is that where they come together?", "qSentId": 496}, {"answer": "Payer.", "docId": "120816pmt", "aSentId": 505, "question": "A good payer?", "qSentId": 504}, {"answer": "There's no payment.", "docId": "120816pmt", "aSentId": 507, "question": "Does he always pay up on time and give you a good tip?", "qSentId": 506}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "120816pmt", "aSentId": 510, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 509}, {"answer": "They all do.", "docId": "120816pmt", "aSentId": 512, "question": "How come he gets a freebie?", "qSentId": 511}, {"answer": "Stop being attached to the outcome.", "docId": "120816pmt", "aSentId": 524, "question": "What are the things I should just forget about doing?", "qSentId": 523}, {"answer": "We never discuss it.", "docId": "120816pmt", "aSentId": 545, "question": "Does he know after all the commitment he's given you, the 100 percent dedication, that you still haven't given him his vote?", "qSentId": 544}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120816pmt", "aSentId": 587, "question": "Did you think anything?", "qSentId": 586}, {"answer": "Unfortunately I have been in a few accidents in my life.", "docId": "120816pmt", "aSentId": 601, "question": "Are you just one of life's naturally unlucky guys?", "qSentId": 600}, {"answer": "That would be me, yes.", "docId": "120816pmt", "aSentId": 612, "question": "Although I think one of you was unconscious, right?", "qSentId": 611}]